Finding Aid for Stephen M. Ross School of Business (University of Michigan) records, 1916-2017
Bentley Historical Library
- Floyd A. Bond and Successors Series, 1926-1984; 1960-1979
  - Personal, 1944-1979
    - University of Michigan, 1960-1979
      - Speeches
        - 1962
          - Washington, DC, Association of State University and Land Grant Colleges, "Relationship of the Business Program to Other Units of the Institution", November 13 (Box 100)
          - Syracuse, NY, Syracuse University, December 11 (Box 100)
        - 1963
          - Pontiac, MI, Pontiac Exchange Club, January 13 and Ann Arbor, President's Club, February 22 (Box 100)
          - President's Conference, "The True Executive", April 2 (Box 100)
          - Ann Arbor, All Class Dinner, June 6 (Box 100)
          - Ann Arbor, Institute on College and University Administration, "The View from the Dean's Office", June 25 (Box 100)
        - 1964
          - Ann Arbor, Business Administration Conference, "The Executive Type", April 17 (Box 100)
          - Chicago, American Association of Collegiate Schools of Business, May 1 (Box 100)
          - Ann Arbor, Institute of Public Policy, Introductions, May 23 (Box 100)
          - Ann Arbor, Dinner Discussion Group, October 19 (Box 100)
          - Ann Arbor, Harlan Hatcher Introduction, November 11 (Box 100)
        - 1965
          - Ann Arbor, Katholepistemiad, "Higher Education for Business, February 6, and "Survey Research Methods in the Social Sciences", December 11 (Box 100)
          - Detroit, Conference on Industrial Modernization, "Resources to Fight Obsolescence and Increase Profit", April 20 (Box 100)
          - New York, NY, Joint Council on Economic Education, "Economic Education and Schools of Business Administration", April 28 (Box 100)
        - 1966
          - Dearborn, MI, UM-Dearborn MBA Program Meeting, "Preparation for Business Leadership", January 4 (Box 100)
          - Fort Wayne, IN, $55 Million Campaign Dinner Meeting, January 6 (Box 100)
          - Ann Arbor, Graduate School of Business Administration, MBA Orientation Talk, August 28 (Box 100)
          - University of Miami, Commercial Bankers Forum, "Commercial Banks: There Changing Role", November 18 (Box 100)
        - 1967
          - Ann Arbor, "American Enterprise: What Lies Ahead", March 3 (Box 100)
          - Ann Arbor, Graduate School of Business Administration, "The Next 50 Years in Business", October 9 (Box 100)
        - 1968
          - Arizona State University, College of Business Administration Building Dedication, "Preparation for Business Leadership", October 9 (Box 100)
        - 1970
          - Ann Arbor, "Financial Executives Institute, "Educating Tomorrow's Financial Executives", March 23 (Box 100)
        - 1971
          - Benton Harbor, MI, Bankers Conference, "Reflections on the Soviet Economy", April 28 (Box 100)
        - 1976
          - Ann Arbor, "Financing the Impossible", January 29 (Box 100)
        - 1977
          - Ann Arbor, Fall Accounting Conference, October 4 (Box 100)
        - 1978
          - Ann Arbor, Katholepistemiad, February 11 (Box 100)
          - Detroit, Economic Club of Detroit, Introduction of Philip Morrison, October 23 (Box 100)
        - 1979
          - Massachusetts Mutual Life, "Should the U.S. Constitution Require a Balanced Budget?", April 24 (Box 100)
    - Pomona College and Earlier, 1944-1960
      - Activities and Publications, 1949-1959; 10 folders (Box 101)
        (folders generally by academic year)
      - American Economic Association, Standing Committee on Economic Education, 1956-1959 (Box 101)
      - Business Executive Conference, 1958-1960; 2 folders (Box 101)
      - Correspondence, 1947-1960; 4 folders (Box 101)
      - Fund for Adult Education, 1955-1959 (Box 101)
      - Michigan, University of, 1944-1948 (Box 101)
      - Morris B. Pendleton memos, 1956-1959 (Box 101)
      - Western Economic Association, Committee on Economic Education, 1956 (Box 101)
  - Personal, 1949-1984
    The Personal series (1944-84) documents Bond's activities beyond the University of Michigan. Most notable are the papers Bond retained from his involvement with the American Association of Collegiate Schools of Business. There is also information from the Economic Club of Detroit, the Committee for Economic Development (including records from Bond's trip to the Soviet Union), the Committee on Institutional Cooperation, the Educational Testing Service, and the Michigan Council on Economic Education.
    - American Association of Collegiate Schools of Business
      - 1960-1964, 20 folders (Box 86)
      - 1964-1969, 37 folders (Box 87)
      - 1968-1978, 34 folders (Box 88)
    - American Economic Association, 1962-1980; 2 folders (Box 88)
    - Beta Gamma Sigma, 1983 (Box 88)
    - Bond, Floyd
      - Annual Report, 1979-1983 (Box 88)
      - Biographical Information (Box 88)
      - Committees, 1960-1972 (Box 88)
      - Correspondence
        - Commendatory Letters, 1964-1983 (Box 88)
        - Commendatory Letters, 1964-1983; 5 folders (Box 89)
      - General, 1979-1984; 6 folders (Box 89)
    - Cleary College, 1983 (Box 89)
    - Committee for Economic Development
      - General, 1957-1965; 18 folders (Box 89)
      - Business Education Committee, 1957-1965; 11 folders (Box 89)
      - Business Leadership Survey (Preparation for Business Leadership), 1961-1964; 7 folders (Box 90)
      - Task Force on Economic Education, 1960-1964; 12 folders (Box 90)
      - USSR Trip, 1958-1961; 11 folders (Box 90)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (Box 91)
      - General, 1963-1977; 6 folders (Box 91)
      - Racine (Johnson Foundation) Conferences, 1962-1971; 9 folders (Box 91)
    - Dean Floyd A. Bond Fund, 1978 (Box 91)
    - Delta Sigma Pi, 1960-1975 (Box 91)
    - Drab to Sapphire Blue (AACSB), 1969-1975 (Box 91)
    - Economic Club of Detroit, 1966-1983; 19 folders (Box 91)
    - Economic Dinner Group, 1961-1983; 3 folders (Box 92)
    - Economics of Enterprise, 1962 (Box 92)
    - Educational Testing Service, Admission Test for Graduate Study in Business, 1958-1969; 6 folders (Box 92)
    - Export Expansion Council, 1964-1970 (Box 92)
    - Government Accounting Office, 1969-1973 (Box 92)
    - Hall of Fame for Great Americans, 1976 (Box 92)
    - Joint Council on Economic Education, 1961-1968 (Box 92)
    - Joint Legislative Committee on Economic Growth, 1961-1962 (Box 92)
    - Katholepistemiad, 1962-1981 (Box 92)
    - Marathon Scholarship Committee, 1977-1980 (Box 92)
    - McKinsey Foundation Awards, 1960-1961 (Box 92)
    - Michigan Council on Economic Education, 1959-1967; 4 folders (Box 92)
    - Michigan Council on Economic Education, 1964-1969; 4 folders (Box 93)
    - National Association of State University and Land Grant Colleges, 1966-1972; 5 folders (Box 93)
    - Pomona College, 1949-1958 (Box 93)
    - Publicity (Box 93)
    - Recognition Dinner (Box 93)
    - Robert S. Craig Associates, 1978 (Box 93)
    - Something for Seniors, 1983 (Box 93)
    - Special Lecturers, 1959-1970; 2 boxes (Box 94)
    - Scholarships, 1962-1971; 2 boxes (Box 94)
  - School Records, 1961-1982
    The School Records Series is a small topical file which includes files on the history of accounting at Michigan, student unrest, grade distributions, dedication of the Paton Center and other administrative subjects.
    - Academic Staff Questionnaire, 1968 (Box 100)
    - Accounting at UM, History of, 1976 (Box 100)
    - Administrative Organization, 1962-1972 (Box 100)
    - Budget Planning, 1972-1976 (Box 100)
    - Business Economic Group, 1972-1981; 3 folders (Box 100)
    - Donald C. Cook Professorship, 1976-1978 (Box 100)
    - Farewell to Deans, 1978 (Box 100)
    - Grade Distributions, 1978-1982 (Box 100)
    - Griffon, Clare, Review of "Business Education Ideas", 1960 (Box 100)
    - Paton Center Dedication, June 11, 1976 (Box 100)
    - Reports of Special Committees, 1961-1962 (Box 100)
    - Research-Organization, 1961 (Box 100)
    - Student Evaluations (of courses taught by Bond), 1982 (Box 100)
    - Student Unrest, Documentation for President, 1970-1971 (Box 100)
- Gilbert A. Whitaker Files, 1925-1991
  The Gilbert A. Whitaker Files subgroup (5 linear feet) spans the years 1925 to 1991; most of the material covers the period of Whitaker's tenure as dean, 1979 and 1990. The subgroup is divided into three series: Committees, Topical files, and Visual Material.
  - Committees, 1925-1991
    The Committees series (1.6 linear feet) is arranged alphabetically by committee title. The series documents administrative decision-making at the school: the development of policy regarding curriculum, hiring practices, and relations with the business community. The "Committee Roles and Responsibilities" folder provides a succinct overview of each committee's purpose and organizational role, while the "Visiting Committee" files serve as an annual summary of changes and developments at the school from 1979 to 1988.
    Some "Executive Committee" files will remain closed for thirty years from their date of creation, because they contain confidential personnel information; "Faculty Meeting Minutes" created between 1928 and 1949 have been closed for 75 years, to protect students' confidentiality. The files for these committees which remain open, however, provide insight into decision-making processes at the school.
    Faculty Meeting Minutes from the 1920s, and Curriculum Committee Minutes created between 1947 and 1961, supplement earlier accessions from the Stevenson and Bond administrations.
    - Academic and Admissions Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 102)
    - Administrative Committee, 1988-1990; 2 folders (Box 102)
    - Administrative Sub-Committee, 1984-1988; 2 folders (Box 102)
    - Affirmative Action Committee, 1979-1984 (Box 102)
    - Committee Roles and Responsibilities, 1990-1991 (Box 102)
    - Coordinating Committee for Business Programs Minutes, 1981-1984 (Box 102)
    - Core Course Coordinating Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 102)
    - Curriculum Committee Minutes, indexed, 1947-1961; 4 folders (Box 102)
    - Curriculum Committee Minutes, 1979-1984; 3 folders (Box 102)
    - Doctoral Studies Committee, 1979-1981; 2 folders (Box 102)
    - Executive Committee Minutes, 1975-1988
      - 1975-1976, 2 folders (Box 106)
      - 1976-1978, 2 folders (Box 102)
      - Executive Committee Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 106)
      - Executive Committee Minutes, 1980-1988; 5 folders (Box 106)
    - Executive Committee, Promotions and tenure, 1981-1984; 2 folders (Box 106)
    - Executive Committee Faculty Evaluations, 1986 (Box 106)
    - Faculty Meeting Minutes
      - 1925-1928 (Box 102)
      - 1928-1949, 9 folders (Box 106)
      - 1949-1962, 4 folders (Box 102)
      - 1979-1987, 9 folders (Box 102)
    - Management Education Policy Committee, 1979-1985 (Box 103)
    - Standing Committee Membership Lists, 1973 (Box 103)
    - Visiting Committee, 1979-1988; 7 folders (Box 103)
    - Visiting Committee, 1984 (Box 142)
  - Topical files, 1962-1991; 2.6 linear feet
    The Topical files series (2.6 linear feet) is arranged alphabetically by subject, and covers the years 1962 to 1991 (bulk dates: 1978-1989). The series contains information on a wide variety of topics, from budgets and endowment data to sabbatical reports and curriculum assessments; the latter are listed by academic department or degree title, for example "Accounting", or "BBA".
    The "Faculty Retreat" files are of particular interest, as they include reports from faculty work groups which contain assessments of the school's effectiveness, as well as discussions of long-term planning and goals.
    The "AIESEC" [International Association of Students in Economics and Business Management] and "Student Council Minutes" files document aspects of student activities at the school.
    Files pertaining to Gilbert R Whitaker, Jr.'s deanship document the School of Business Administration during the mid-1980s. The "Whitaker -Five Year Plans/Goals Discussion Paper" contains Whitaker's assessment of the school's strengths and weaknesses, along with his long-term plans to promote the school's quality and reputation.
    - AACSB (American Assembly of Collegiate Schools of Business) Resurvey, 1975; 2 folders (Box 103)
    - AACSB Self Study, 1978-1979 (Box 103)
    - AISEC (International Association of Students in Economics and Business Management), 1979-1984 (Box 103)
    - Accounting, 1983 (Box 103)
    - Actuarial Science Fellowship Fund, Annual Reports, 1971-1978 (Box 103)
    - Actuarial Science Program, 1962-1977; 1980-1985; 2 folders (Box 103)
    - Actuarial Science Review Committee Report, 1983 (Box 103)
    - Admissions, 1981-1984 (Box 103)
    - Admissions, enrollment statistics, 1981-1984 (Box 103)
    - Affirmative Action Reports, 1971-1974 (Box 103)
    - Alumni Society, 1980-1983 (Box 103)
    - Annual Reports, 1979-1981 (Box 103)
    - Application Status Summaries, 1979 (Box 103)
    - BBA (Bachelor of Business Administration) Study Team Report, 1989 (Box 103)
    - Benton Bequest, 1985 (Box 103)
    - Budget, 1979-1986; 7 folders (Box 103)
    - Budget-19 Computing Services, 1985-1986 (Box 103)
    - Building Addition-19 Planning, 1980-1985; 3 folders (Box 103)
    - Burroughs Impact Research Project, 1984 (Box 103)
    - Business German (language course), 1980 (Box 103)
    - Business Leadership Award, 1979-1985; 2 folders (Box 104)
    - Capital Campaign Kickoff, 1981 (Box 104)
    - Capital Campaign Literature, 1981 (Box 104)
    - Capital Campaign Progress Reports, 1981-1985 (Box 104)
    - Center for Continuing Education of Women, 1979-1983 (Box 104)
    - China Exchanges, 1980-1982 (Box 104)
    - Commencement Planning, 1979 (Box 104)
    - Computer and Information Systems (CIS) Group, 1979-1982 (Box 104)
    - Computer Budget, 1982-1983 (Box 104)
    - Computer Services, 1983-1984 (Box 104)
    - Dedication of New Building, 1984 (Box 104)
    - Development Office, 1977-1981 (Box 104)
    - Division of Research, 1982-1983 (Box 104)
    - Doctoral Program and Scholarship Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 104)
    - Enrollment Data, 1965-1983; 3 folders (Box 104)
    - Enrollment Studies and Forecasts, 1960-1965 (Box 104)
    - Evening MBA Program, 1978-1979 (Box 104)
    - Executive Management Education, 1976-1983; 2 folders (Box 104)
    - Executive Program-England, 1981,1984 (Box 104)
    - Faculty Lists, 1978-1987; 2 folders (Box 104)
    - Faculty Retreat, 1987; 2 folders (Box 104)
    - Faculty Retreat, 1990 (Box 104)
    - Faculty Group Evaluations, 1984 (Box 113)
    - Faculty Retreat, 1985; 3 folders (Box 113)
    - Faculty Retreat, March 1987 (Box 113)
    - Faculty Retreat, September 1987 (Box 113)
    - Faculty Retreat, 1989 (Box 113)
    - Faculty Retreat, 1996 (Box 142)
    - Financial Aid, 1980-1984 (Box 104)
    - Funding Memoranda, 1970-1974 (Box 104)
    - Funding-Sources and Allocation, 1982-1984 (Box 104)
    - General Fund Allocations (printouts), 1979-1983 (Box 104)
    - General Motors, 1979-1982 (Box 104)
    - Grade Distribution, by term (incomplete), 1977-1985 (Box 104)
    - Grievance Procedure, 1983 (Box 104)
    - Harris, J. Ira, 1983-1984 (Box 104)
    - Human Resource Management [Journal], 1982-1983 (Box 104)
    - Humanities PhDs-Business Training, 1979 (Box 104)
    - Independent Business Research Institute of Michigan (IBRIM), 1981 (Box 104)
    - Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations (ILIR), 1981-1982 (Box 104)
    - Japan Fundraising, 1980-1985 (Box 105)
    - Library Budget, 1983 (Box 105)
    - Library Planning and Administration, 1979-1981 (Box 105)
    - Library Staff Evaluations, 1982-1983 (Box 105)
    - MBA Grading Policy, 1990 (Box 105)
    - MBA Strategy Files (Box 113)
    - McInally Lecture, 1984 (Box 105)
    - Minority Student Admissions Statistics, 1981-1984 (Box 105)
    - Owens-Corning Fiberglas Corporation, 1983 (Box 105)
    - Perry, Alexander P. (Student Investment Fund), 1983 (Box 105)
    - Planning and Evaluation Responses, 1984 (Box 105)
    - Promotions and Tenure, 1978-1987; 9 folders (Box 106)
    - Promotions-statistics for minorities and women, 1978-1979 (Box 105)
    - Real Estate Education, 1981-1984 (Box 105)
    - Research Excellence Fund, 1986 (Box 105)
    - Retail Marketing Program, 1980 (Box 105)
    - Sabbatical Reports, 1984 (Box 105)
    - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA), 1984-1987 (Box 105)
    - Shapiro, Harold, 1979-1980 (Box 105)
    - Small Business Consulting Group Proposal, 1984 (Box 105)
    - Strategic Planning Retreat, 1987 (Box 142)
    - Student Council Minutes, 1979-1982 (Box 105)
    - Summer Research Proposal Assessments, 1981; 1986 (Box 105)
    - Task Force on the MBA, 1987; 1989 (Box 105)
    - Teaching Assistant Expenditures, 1979-1981 (Box 105)
    - Teaching Faculty Planning Model, 1979 (Box 105)
    - US-Japan Communications Program, 1983-1984 (Box 105)
    - Washington Campus Program, 1979-1985 (Box 105)
    - Whirlpool Corporation, 1984 (Box 105)
    - Whitaker, Dean Gilbert R., Jr
      - Correspondence re:salaries, 1981-1982 (Box 106)
      - Correspondence (incomplete), 1987 (Box 105)
      - Correspondence list, chronological, 1987 (Box 105)
      - Five Year Plans/Goals Discussion Paper, 1984 (Box 105)
      - Memoranda, 1985-1986 (Box 105)
    - White, B. Joseph, 1990-1991 (Box 105)
    - Winkelman Chair in Retail Marketing, 1980-1981 (Box 105)
  - Reports, 1969-1995
    - "Ad Hoc Committee on Long Range Goals and Organization of School,", 1969 (Box 113)
    - "Development of Programs for Professional Education in Management,", 1992 (Box 113)
    - "Improving the Business School PhD Program,", 1992 (Box 113)
    - MBA Redesign of Materials, 1985 (Box 113)
    - "Optimization Programs at UM,", 1973 (Box 113)
    - "Partnership for Economic Development Outreach,", 1995 (Box 113)
    - "Peer Competition: Challenge for the '90s" (Box 113)
- Audiovisual Material, 1926-2014; undated
  The Audiovisual Material subgroup (25 linear feet and 1 oversize folder) includes photographs and slides of Business School deans and faculty members, buildings and facilities, school sponsored events, and images that were printed is Dividend Magazine as well as a microfilm reel recording items placed in the Business Administration building cornerstone. The Sound Recordings consist of recordings of a number of conferences and lectures. The Moving Image Recordings series contains video tapes depicting student life, conferences, development materials and other promotional materials for the school. The Oversized Photographs and Awards series contains 18 oversized images, and the Oversize Posters series contains 1 event poster.
  The Audiovisual Materials subgroup is organized into nine series: Photographs, Slides, Drawings, Dividend Magazine Microfilm, Sound Recrodings, Moving Image Recordings, Oversized Photographs and Images, and Oversize Posters.
  - Photographs, 1926-1985
    The photographs include pictures of Deans Stevenson, Bond, and Whitaker, as well as several other faculty members, special lecturers and award winners, and photos of various buildings constructed for the school.
    A large selection of print and digital photos of students, faculty, alumni, student life, events and other aspects of the school were added in 2018.
    - Bank Training Program, 1953 (Box 95)
    - Bond, Dean Floyd A (Box 95)
    - Buildings
      - Assembly Hall (Box 95)
      - Construction, 1947-1948; 2 folders (Box 95)
      - Cornerstone Laying (Box 95)
      - Hale Auditorium (Box 95)
      - Interiors, 1949 (Box 95)
      - Negatives, 1949 (Box 95)
      - Paton Center (Box 95)
      - Photograph Album, 1949 (Box 95)
      - Tappan Hall (Box 95)
      - Ross Construction- Exterior, Interior, 2008
      - New Building Preview, 2008
      - New Building, 2008
      - New Building Renderings, undated
      - Blau/Kresge, 2016
      - Tozzi Center, 2005
    - Bureau of Industrial Relations (Box 95)
    - Business Leadership Awards (Box 95)
    - Class of, 1929 (Box 95)
    - Class photos (oversize), 1926-1942; 17 oversize items (Object 1-17)
    - Dean's Reception, August 31, 1965 (Box 95)
    - Executive Development Programs, 1955; 1956 (Box 95)
    - Faculty
      - General (Box 95)
      - 1958-1959 (Box 95)
        (most with biographical material)
      - 1966 (Box 95)
      - Retired (Box 95)
      - Deans and Committee Chairs, 2008
      - Faculty Awards, 2009
      - Faculty Awards, 2003
      - Staff Photographs, 1 of 2, 2002
      - Staff Photographs, 2 of 2, 2002
    - General Mills Meeting (Box 95)
    - Groups, miscellaneous (Box 95)
    - Hale, Clayton G (Box 95)
    - Honorary Degrees (Box 95)
    - Kresge, S.S. Professorship (Box 95)
    - Marathon Scholars (Box 95)
    - McInally, William K (Box 95)
    - Public Utility Executive Programs, 1958-1959 (Box 95)
    - Romney, Governor George (Box 95)
    - Stevenson, Dean Russell A (Box 95)
    - Business Leadership Award Recipients, 1979-1985 (Box 105)
    - Whitaker, Dean Gilbert R., Jr., undated (Box 105)
    - Division of Management Education, 1982-1983 (Box 114)
    - Fall Courtyard (Box 114)
    - Marion Leroy (Box 114)
    - 75th Anniversary, 5 volumes
      - Binders 1-4 (Box 114)
      - Binder 5 (Box 114)
    - Marketing Photograph Files
      - Adams,William, undated (Box 129)
      - AACSB Global Forum, undated (Box 129)
      - African Business Development Corps, undated (Box 129)
      - Afuah, Allen, undated (Box 129)
      - Ahuja, Gautam, undated (Box 129)
      - Albert, Terri, undated (Box 129)
      - Albright, Madeline, undated (Box 129)
      - Alessi, Alan, undated (Box 129)
      - Alessi Courtyard, undated (Box 129)
      - Alger, David, undated (Box 129)
      - Altmann, Juan Carlos, undated (Box 129)
      - Alumni Clubs
        - Beijing, undated (Box 129)
        - Brazil, undated (Box 129)
        - Chicago, undated (Box 129)
        - Detroit, undated (Box 129)
        - Florida, undated (Box 129)
        - Japan, undated (Box 129)
        - Hong Kong, undated (Box 129)
        - Indonesia, undated (Box 129)
        - Minneapolis, undated (Box 129)
        - New York, undated (Box 129)
        - Northern California, undated (Box 129)
        - San Francisco, undated (Box 129)
        - Seattle, undated (Box 129)
        - South Florida, undated (Box 129)
        - Switzerland, undated (Box 129)
        - Thailand, undated (Box 129)
        - Washington D.C., undated (Box 129)
      - Alumni Group, undated (Box 129)
      - Alumni Service, undated (Box 129)
      - Alumni West Coast Forum, undated (Box 129)
      - Americorps, undated (Box 129)
      - Among Ourselves, undated (Box 129)
      - Anand, Jay, undated (Box 129)
      - Anderson, Eugene, undated (Box 129)
      - Anderson, Shannon, undated (Box 129)
      - Ann Arbor Shots, undated (Box 129)
      - Annual Biz Conference, 2005 (Box 129)
      - Annual Report, 2002 (Box 129)
      - Architecture, undated (Box 129)
      - Architecture- Historic, undated (Box 129)
      - Arneson, Susan R., undated (Box 129)
      - Artzt, Edwin, undated (Box 129)
      - Ashford, Susan, undated (Box 129)
      - Asian Business Conference, undated (Box 129)
      - Augustine, Norman, undated (Box 129)
      - AT Kearney Team, undated (Box 129)
      - Bacdayan, Paul, undated (Box 129)
      - Bagozzi, Richard, undated (Box 129)
      - Baker, James, undated (Box 129)
      - Baker, Robert, undated (Box 129)
      - Baker, Wayne, undated (Box 129)
      - Bala, Chris, undated (Box 129)
      - Banez, Allen, undated (Box 129)
      - Bantel, Karen, undated (Box 129)
      - Barr, George P. Jr., undated (Box 129)
      - Barry, Hank, undated (Box 129)
      - Batra, Rajeev, undated (Box 129)
      - Bayless, Maggie, undated (Box 129)
      - BBA Program, undated (Box 129)